let MOCK_QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: "What for does JavaScript use DOM?",
        answer: "To handle the elements in an HTML page.",
    },

    {
        question: "Where can we use the 'length' attribute?",
        answer: "It's an attribute for arrays and strings.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which variable type does always have global scope?",
        answer: "Variables that are declared as 'var'",
    },

    {
        question: "What do you need so you can use 'await' inside a function?",
        answer: "The function should be declared as 'async'",
    },
    {
        question: "What does DOM mean?",
        answer: "It's an acronym for Document Object Model",
    },
    {
        question: "What are the conditional commands?",
        answer: "They are if-else, switch and the ternary operator",
    },
    {
        question: "What's an arrow function?",
        answer: "It's a function defined without a name, using the structure '() => {}'.",
    },

    {
        question: "How do we create a class in JavaScript?",
        answer: "By using the reserved word 'class' before its name. The class code goes between {}.",
    },

    {
        question: "How to create a subclass in JavaScript?",
        answer: "By using the reserved word 'inherits' before the parent class name.",
    },
    {
        question: "What's the structure for handling errors?",
        answer: "It's try {} catch(error){} finally{}",
    },

];